Find the Fifi file in Ametar and Vimeo VR. Double-click on the Fifi file or drag it to the 3D window.
In the practice file B-Basic-A-Tissue, find the Tissue.dxf file and double-click on it or drag it to the 3D window.
In the menu, click OK.
In the 2D window, you can see a gray model shadow.
Select all panels and move the panel to the virtual model shadow.
Now you can see that there is only half of the panel.
You need to duplicate the other half.
In the 2D tool bar, select the Edit panel tool.
Right-click on the front middle line.
In the menu, select the Edit panel tool.
Right-click on the other half.
Do the same thing on the back middle line.
The sleeves are two sleeves.
You can't use the Edit panel tool here.
In the 2D tool bar, select the Edit panel tool.
Right-click on the sleeve.
In the menu, select the Cron link panel.
Right-click on the panel and select Edit panel.
The panel is aligned like this.
When you modify the panel or create a sewing line on one side, the other side will also operate the same way.
Press Shift and the panel will be aligned.
The level is placed on the other side.
In the 3D tool bar, select Rearrange 2D.
All the arrangement positions will be synchronized to the 3D window.
In the 3D ruler, select Show Arrangement Point.
The model arrangement point will be displayed.
Parts of the arrangement points are blocked by the panel.
In the 2D window, select all the panels.
Press Ctrl-A to select all the panels.
Place the panel on the arrangement point where it is blocked.
On the front panel, select the left button.
Move the mouse to the arrangement point of the virtual model.
On the arrangement point, select the left button.
Place the panel.
Press the shortcut key to select the rear view.
Select the rear panel.
On the rear arrangement point, select the left button.
Place the panel on the back of the model.
On the right hand, select the mouse and then move the mouse to the lower angle and press Ctrl,
press Ctrl again.
Click on the II to scroll on to the bottom
Base the foster apartment,
select icon for the stage and select the second button.
Extrude the trois-channel.
Select the polygon.
In the traveller mode, the center pin,
select Spar.
Press Ctrl-D to close the top cloud.
Scroll to the top.
Pick button, selectissa biz.
Click the button magic test,
click command button.
In the 2D tool bar, select the linear sewing tool, sew the shoulder line, the side seam, and the sleeve.
Each machine needs to sew two lines to complete a set of sewing.
When sewing, pay attention to the direction of the sewing line.
After sewing the big body and the sleeve, the collar and the big body are sewed.
First sew the front collar and the front piece, pay attention to the direction of the sewing line.
Press the shortcut key 8 to rotate the view to the rear view.
Using the linear sewing tool, sew into the 3D window.
There is a gap between the baskets.
The linear sewing needs to be used here with a stroke of N.
First click on the back collar and close to the back center.
Complete a set of sewing.
Press Shift and select N.
First click on the back collar and close to the back center.
Rotate the view and click next to the side seam.
Press Shift and select N and complete the linear sewing.
The line sewing is completed.
After finishing the sewing,
After finishing the simulation, turn off the simulation and find the post file in the Aventa FemaleVR file from the
picture window.
Double-click on the FV203 file or insert it into the 3D window.
Play the dialogue light and click OK.
Change the position of the virtual model to a vertical position.
Find the picture window Fabric.
Insert the NEAT file into the object window and cover it on FemaleVR.
Activate the simulation and then close the simulation.
Close the simulation.
Next, we will explain the simulation of FV203.
Open the FV203 by clicking the FB app.
Locate the FB app in the FB menu bar and press FB.
Then press OK.
Next, the simulation of FV203 will run smoothly.
Try to add the FB app in the FB FB information window window.
Press OK.
Then, the FB application will go to the FB app.
click OK.
Press OK.
The FB application will go to the FB FB application.
Through the FB application, the app will show a light blue color.
Click OK.
Finally, the simulation of FV203 will start.
Click on the object window, and then on the female VR, and then on the 3D costume.
In the 3D tool bar, select the tool to increase the quality of the costume.
Increase the quality of the 3D costume.
Open the dialogue box and click OK.
Open the model and apply the settings to the 3D costume.
In the object window, click on the plant.
In the attribute editor, this plant-related attribute will appear.
Click on the color bar next to the color.
A dialogue box will appear.
You can use the small
tool to extract all the colors in the page.
You can also enter RGB values.
Text here will be use to do the work.
Ct One object Vision Lighting
Ct Color
C& Photo
Diodic
Italian
Totally
Back-abound
Nous
Le